Finding aid for the Jerry Lewis papers LSC.2124
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 3: Legislative Files, 1969-2013
  - Subseries 3.3. US Congress, National Subject Files, 1979-2013
    - Congress: Roth–Lewis Budget Reform, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Congress: Roth–Lewis Budget Reform, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Congress: Roth–Lewis Budget Reform, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Congress: Roth–Lewis Budget Reform, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Congress: Ways and Means, Hank Brown, 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Defense: Appropriations, 1992, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Defense: Appropriations FY00, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Defense: Appropriations FY02, Supplemental, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Defense: Appropriations FY06, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Defense: Appropriations FY12, 2011 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Defense: Appropriations Requests FY13, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Defense: Contractors, MZM, 2004-2005 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Defense: Civilian Health & Medical Program (CHAMPUS), 1980-1981 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Defense: F-22 Raptor FY00, 1997-1999 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Defense: F-22 Raptor FY00, 1997-1999 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Defense: F-22 Raptor FY00, 1997-1999 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Defense: F-22 Raptor FY00, 1997-1999 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Defense: F-22 Raptor FY00, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Defense: F-22 Raptor FY00, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Defense: F-22 Raptor FY00, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Defense: F-22 Raptor FY00, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Defense: F-22 Raptor FY00, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Defense: F-22 Raptor FY00, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Defense: F-22 Raptor FY00, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Defense: F-22 Raptor FY00, 1999-2000 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Defense: F-22 Raptor FY00, 1999-2000 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Defense: F-22 Raptor, Testing, 1999-2001 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Defense: F-22 Raptor, Air Force Response, 1999-2001 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Defense: F-22 Raptor, 1999-2003 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Defense: F-22 Raptor, 1999-2003 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Defense: F-22 Raptor, 1999-2003 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Defense: F-22 Raptor FY01, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Defense: F-22 Raptor FY02, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Defense: Defense Appropriations FY07, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Defense: INF Treaty, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Defense: KC-45 Tanker Briefing, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Defense: Military Medical Services, PTSD, 2012 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Defense: Military Spouse Protection Act, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Defense: Persian Gulf, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Defense: Predator, 2006-2009 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Defense: Unmanned Combat Vehicles, 2000-2004 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Defense: Unmanned Combat Vehicles, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Defense: US Navy, LFA Sonar, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Defense: Veterans Affairs, Homelessness, 2011-2012 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - District of Columbia: Appropriations FY00, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - District of Columbia: Appropriations FY01, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - District of Columbia: Appropriations FY02, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - District of Columbia: Appropriations FY03, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - District of Columbia: Appropriations FY06, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - District of Columbia: Barracks Row, 2001-2005 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - District of Columbia: Barracks Row, 2001-2005 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Economy/Business: Budget and Appropriations Background, 2010 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Economy/Business: Credit Lyonnais, 2002-2004 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Economy/Business: Federal Maritime Commission, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Economy/Business: Financial Services Appropriations FY11, 2010 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Economy/Business: Financial Services Appropriations FY12, 2011 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Economy/Business: Department of Commerce, 2005-2007 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Economy/Business: Financial Services FY08, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Economy/Business: Firefighter Bill, Tax Exemptions, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Economy/Business: Miscellaneous Subjects, 1988-1992 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Economy/Business: Monetary Policy, Gold Coin Act, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Economy/Business: Monetary Policy, Gold Coin Act, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Economy/Business: Monetary Policy, Gold Coin Act, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Economy/Business: Opportunity Nation, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Economy/Business: Pension Plan Protection Act, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Economy/Business: Steel Industry, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Economy/Business: Steel Industry, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Economy/Business: TARP, 2009 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Economy/Business: Task Force on Economic Policy, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Economy/Business: Taxes, US Citizens Abroad, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Election Assistance Commission, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Education Hearing, 2012 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Appropriations, Foreign Operations FY03, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Appropriations, Foreign Operations, Supplemental FY03, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Appropriations, Foreign Operations FY03, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Appropriations, Foreign Operations FY04, 2002-2003 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Appropriations, Foreign Operations FY04, 2002-2003 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Appropriations, Foreign Operations FY06, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Appropriations, Foreign Operations FY08, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Appropriations, Foreign Operations FY10, 2009 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Burma, Project Old Soldier, 1994-1999 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Burma, Project Old Soldier, 1994-1999 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Burma, Project Old Soldier, 1994-1999 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Burma, Project Old Soldier, 1994-1999 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Burma, Project Old Soldier, 1994-1999 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: China, Rare Earth Mining, Molycorp, 2011 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Colombia, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Cyprus, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: India, Education, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Iran, Visas, HCR 248, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Iraq, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Iraq, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Iraq, International Education (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Jordan, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Latin America, Contra Aid, Lewis Plan, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Mexico Trip, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Mexico Trip, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Mexico Trip, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Mexico Trip, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Mexico Trip, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Mexico Trip, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Mexico Trip, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Middle East, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Miscellaneous, 1988-1992 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Millennium Challenge Account, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: Philippines, Election Delegation, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: State Department Background, 2004-2009 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: State Department Publications, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Foreign Aid/Operations: USAID Hearing, 2002-2003 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Freedom of Speech, 1986, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Freedom of Speech, Braille Playboy Controversy, 1980, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Freedom of Speech, Press Shield Law, 1978-1981 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Freedom of Speech, Press Shield Law, 1978-1981 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Freedom of Speech, Press Shield Law, 1978-1981 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Freedom of Speech, Theta Delta Chi, 1990-1994 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Hispanic Serving Institutions, HACU, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Housing and Urban Development: Appropriations FY03, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Housing and Urban Development: Appropriations FY08, 2007 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Housing and Urban Development: Appropriations FY08, 2007 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Housing and Urban Development: Appropriations FY09, 2008 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Housing and Urban Development: Community Action Partnership of San Bernardino, 2006-2007 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Housing and Urban Development: Expanding American Homeownership Act, 2007 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Housing and Urban Development: Fraud, 1996-2001 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Housing and Urban Development: Fraud, 1996-2001 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Immigration: Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Immigration: Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Immigration: State Criminal Alien Assistance Program, 2011 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Jerry Lewis Bills, Miscellaneous, 2001-2010 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Jerry Lewis Bills, Miscellaneous, 2001-2010 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Jerry Lewis Issues, Miscellaneous, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Labor: Appropriations, 1992-1995 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Labor: Appropriations, 1992-1995 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Labor: Appropriations FY06, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Labor: Appropriations, Labor, HHS, Education FY09, 2008 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Labor: Appropriations, Labor, HHS, Education FY12, 2011 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Labor: Careers Act, 1995-1996 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Labor: Clinton Striker Replacement Executive Order, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Labor: Davis–Bacon Act, 1993-1995 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Labor: Davis–Bacon Act, 1993-1995 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Labor: Davis–Bacon Act, 1993-1995 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Labor: Davis–Bacon Act Repeal, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Labor: Fair Labor Standards Act, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Labor: International Labor Affairs Bureau, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Labor: Migrant and Seasonal Agricultural Worker Protection Act, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Labor: Minimum Wage Increase, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Labor: National Labor Relations Act, 1993-1995 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Labor: National Right to Work, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Labor: Occupational Safety and Health Administration, 1992-1995 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Labor: Reemployment Act, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Labor: Striker Replacement, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Labor: Team Act, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Labor: Unemployment Insurance Act, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Land, Water, Energy, Environment: Arctic National Wildlife Refuge, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Land, Water, Energy, Environment: Energy, 2007 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Land, Water, Energy, Environment: Forest, 1988-1991, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Land, Water, Energy, Environment: Interior Subcommittee, 2009 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Land, Water, Energy, Environment: Nuclear Waste, Yucca Mountain, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Land, Water, Energy, Environment: Paleontology Bill, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Land, Water, Energy, Environment: Radon, 2000-2002 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Land, Water, Energy, Environment: Radon, 2000-2002 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Land, Water, Energy, Environment: Radon, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Line Item Veto, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Major League Baseball Strike, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Medical: Osteoporosis, 1989-1990 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Muscular Dystrophy Association, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - NASA, 1985-1986 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - NASA, 1985-1986 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - National Issues, Miscellaneous, 1989-1991 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - National Public Radio, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - NPR Funding, 2011 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Political Essays, 1984-1991 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Public Aid: HR 5749, HR 2642, HR 3021, 2008 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Public Aid: Social Security, 2002-2011 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Public Health: Affordable Care Act, 2009-2012 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Public Health: AIDS Commission, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Public Health: Avian Flu, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Public Health: Catastrophic Insurance, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Public Health: CDC Hearing FY05, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Public Health: HR 2427 Drug Reimportation, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Public Health: H1N1 Flu, 2009 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Public Health: Labor, HHS, Education Hearings, 2009-2010 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Public Health: Labor, HHS, Education Hearings FY12, 2011 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Public Health: Labor, HHS, Education Hearings FY12, FY13, 2012 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Public Health: HIV/AIDS, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Public Health: HIV/AIDS, USAID, 2008 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Public Health: Influenza Preparedness Act, 2005-2006 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Public Health: Influenza Preparedness Act, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Public Health: Mental Health, Homelessness, 2003-2004 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Public Health: Mental Health, Homelessness, 2003-2004 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Public Health: Mental Health, 1988-1991 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Public Health: NIH Common Fund, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Public Health: Optivus Proton Therapy Center, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Public Health: Pandemic Preparedness, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Public Health: Pandemic Preparedness, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Public Health: Prescription Drug Bill, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Public Health: Prescription Drug Bill, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Public Health: Schwarzenegger, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Public Health: Stem Cell Research, 2004-2005 (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - Public Health: UCLA School of Public Health, 2007 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Senate Bill 1639-3 (2 pages), Framed Text, Signed by Tip O'Neill, Strom Thurmond, and Ronald Reagan, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - September 11 Talking Points, 2004 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Telecommunications Act of 1996, HR 1555, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Telecommunications Act of 1996, HR 1555, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Telecommunications Act of 1996, HR 1555, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Telecommunications Act of 1996, HR 1555, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Telecommunications Act of 1996, HR 1555, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Telecommunications Act of 1996, HR 1555, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Telecommunications Act of 1996, HR 1555, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Telecommunications Act of 1996, HR 1555, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Telecommunications Act of 1996, HR 1555, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Telecommunications: Broadband Internet Transmission Bill, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Telecommunications: FCC Hearing, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Transportation: Appropriations FY05, FY06, 2004-2005 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Transportation: Appropriations FY07, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Transportation: Appropriations Hearing, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - USPS Appropriations FY12, 2011 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Washington Center Projects, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Harry Truman Postage Stamp, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Series 4: Media, 1961-2012
  This subseries contains all of the video tapes, photographs, and books that were maintained by Lewis's congressional office. The videos are mostly of appearances made by Jerry Lewis on various national and local television programs. In addition, there are a number of videos of endorsements of Jerry Lewis by various other political figures and even some copies of commercials that were broadcast in support of his 1978 congressional run. Most of the videos are in VHS format, but there are also some Betamax and U-Matic tapes. Most of the photos were taken of Lewis posing with constituents, celebrities, and other political figures during official events. In addition, there are also a number of photographs of Lewis taken while on official travel, including congressional delegation visits.
  This series is organized alphabetically by subject when possible.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Audiovisual materials must be digitized before use.
  - Bound Copies of Appropriations Bills, FY01-FY08, 2001-2008 (Box 57, Folder unknown container)
  - Video: Appearances, Events, News Programs, 1988-2004 (Box 58, Folder unknown container)
    44 VHS Tapes
  - Video: Appearances, Events, News Programs, 1991, 2001-2006 (Box 59, Folder unknown container)
    26 VHS Tapes, 11 Betamax Tapes, 1 Sony DVCAM Tape
  - Video: Appearances, Events, News Programs, 1988-2005 (Box 60, Folder unknown container)
    36 VHS Tapes, 1 Betamax Tape, 2 DVDs
  - Video: Appearances, Events, News Programs, 1988-2003 (Box 61, Folder unknown container)
  - Video: Endorsements, Presidential Messages, News Programs, 1985-2001 (Box 62, Folder unknown container)
    2 Betamax Tapes, 4 DVDs, 10 U-Matic Tapes: 3 KCA-05 Ampex 187; 1 KCA-20 BRS; 1 UCA 60; 1 UCA 10; 1 10 BRS; 2 MBR 30; and 1 MBR 20s.
  - Video: 1978 Election Commercials, NASA Challenger Report (1983), Other, 1978-1983 (Box 63, Folder unknown container)
    6 U-Matic Video Tapes: 4 UCA 30; 2 UCA 20; 1 Unknown
  - Photos: Breakfast with Bill Bennett, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Photos: Congressional Delegations and Other Official Travel, 1979-2012 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Photos: Congressional Delegation, Speaker of the House, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Photos: Congressional Delegation, Speaker of the House, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Photos: Congressional Delegation, Gingrich, Ireland and Germany, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Photos: Congressional Delegation, Gingrich, Ireland and Germany, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Photos: Congressional Delegation, Gingrich, Ireland and Germany, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Photos: Congressional Delegation, Gingrich, Ireland and Germany, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Photos: Congressional Delegation, Gingrich, Ireland and Germany, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Photos: GOP Conference Volume 1, c. 1988 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Photos: GOP Conference Volume 1, c. 1988 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Photos: GOP Conference Volume 2, c. 1988 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Photos: GOP Conference Volume 2, c. 1988 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Photos: GOP Conference Volume 2, c. 1988 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Photos: Honduras Conference, Peru, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Assembly Farewell, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Assembly Photos, 1969-1978 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1961-2012 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1961-2012 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1961-2012 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1961-2012 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1969-2012 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1979-2012 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1979-2012 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1979-2012 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1979-2012 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1979-2012 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1979-2012 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, Private Event, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1979-2012 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1979-2012 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1979-2012 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1979-2012 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1979-2012 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1979-2012 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1979-2012 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1979-2012 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1979-2012 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1979-2012 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1979-2012 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1979-2012 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1979-2012 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1979-2012 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, 1979-2012 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, Copper Mountain College Foundation, 2006 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Events, New York, Family and Staff Party, c. 1987 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis and Arlene Lewis, 1979-1993 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Fundraiser, c. 1990 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Fundraiser, c. 1990 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis on the House Floor, 1990-2012 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis on the House Floor, 1990-2012 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Portraits, 1969-2012 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Portraits, 1969-2012 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Portraits, 1969-2012 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Portraits, 1969-2012 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Portraits, 1969-2012 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Portraits, 1969-2012 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Portraits, 1969-2012 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Portraits, 2000-2012 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Travel, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Travel, Various Military Visits, 1981-1996 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Travel, Various Military Visits, 1981-1996 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Travel, NASA Launch, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis Travel, US Virgin Islands, St. Croix, c. 2005 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Celebrities, 1969-1999 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Celebrities, 1969-1999 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Celebrities, Bono and Sela Ward, c. 2005 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Constituents, 1979-2012 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Constituents, 1979-2012 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Constituents, 1979-2012 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Constituents, 1979-2012 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Constituents, 1979-2012 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Constituents, 1979-2012 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Constituents, 1979-2012 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Constituents, 1979-2012 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Other Congressmen, 1979-2012 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Other Congressmen, 1979-2012 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Other Political Leaders, 1972-2012 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Other Political Leaders, 1979-2012 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Other Political Leaders, 1979-2012 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Other Political Leaders, 1979-2012 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Other Political Leaders, 1979-2012 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Other Political Leaders, 1979-2012 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Other Political Leaders, 1979-2012 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Other Political Leaders, 1979-2012 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Other Political Leaders, 1979-2012 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Other Political Leaders, 1979-2012 (Box 80, Folder 4)